<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fitness Buddy</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_fitness">Fitness</string>
    <string name="unit">Cm</string>
    <string name="femaletext">Female</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">YOUR_WEB_CLIENT_ID_HERE</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="startingheight">170</string>
    <string name="startingweight">55</string>
    <string name="startingage">22</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="height">Height</string>
    <string name="calculate_your_bmi">Calculate Your BMI</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="splashurl">https://lottiefiles.com/24366-workout-monkey-stay-healthy</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="quote1">The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.</string>
    <string name="quote2">Once you learn to quit, it becomes a habit.</string>
    <string name="quote3">A year from now you may wish you had started today.</string>
    <string name="quote4">Look in the mirror. That’s your competition.</string>
    <string name="quote5">A feeble body weakens the mind.</string>
    <string name="quote6">Put all excuses aside and remember this: You are capable.</string>
    <string name="quote7">Reading is to the mind what exercise is to the body.</string>
    <string name="quote8">Success is what comes after your stop making excuses.</string>
    <string name="quote9">The pain you feel today will be the strength you feel tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="quote10">A champion is someone who gets up when they can’t.</string>
    <string name="quote11">Get comfortable with being uncomfortable!</string>
    <string name="quote12">No pain, no gain.</string>
    <string name="pushup">Pushups are a simple and effective bodyweight movement that can help increase strength in your upper body and core.</string>
    <string name="pullup">The pull-up is a closed-chain movement where the body is suspended by the hands and pulls up</string>
    <string name="squats">Strength exercise in which the trainee lowers their hips from a standing position and then stands back up</string>
    <string name="tplank">Inner core exercise which helps reduce body fat and increase core strength</string>
    <string name="deadbug">The dead bug is a bodyweight exercise that targets your abdominal muscles.</string>
    <string name="skipping">User jumps avoiding the incoming rope to increase stamina and it serves as warmup</string>
    <string name="heavysquats">Strength exercise of lower body done but using weights to improve legs,calf,thighs</string>
    <string name="splitjump">Split jumps are a plyometric exercise that strengthen the glutes and leg muscles</string>
    <string name="virkshasana">Tree Pose is a balancing asana</string>
    <string name="cobrasana">Gentle backbend practiced from a face-down position that warms and strengthens the spine while opening the chest</string>
    <string name="pranayama">The practice of pranayama involves breathing exercises and patterns.</string>
    <string name="yogasana">This asana is a meditation on determination and perseverance, as well as commitment.</string>
    <string name="utkatasana1"> It is a strengthening and heat-building asana</string>
    <string name="tvmar">Calisthenics will be added soon. Don\'t forget to drink water and stay hydrated</string>
    <string name="moderate_thinness">Diet Recommendation: Increase your calorie intake by consuming more protein-rich foods like lean meats, fish, eggs, dairy products, nuts, and seeds. Incorporate healthy fats from sources like avocados, olive oil, and nuts.</string>
    <string name="severe_thinness">Diet Recommendation: Include more fruits, vegetables, lean proteins, and healthy fats in your diet. Avoid high-calorie and processed foods.</string>
    <string name="mild_thinness">Diet Recommendation: Focus on nutrient-dense foods such as whole grains, lean proteins, fruits, vegetables, and healthy fats. Ensure you\'re eating enough calories to maintain a healthy weight.</string>
    <string name="normal_diet">No specific diet recommendation needed. However, it\'s essential to maintain a balanced diet with a variety of nutrient-rich foods to support overall health and well-being.</string>
    <string name="overweight_diet">Diet Recommendation: Limit high-calorie, sugary, and processed foods. Focus on portion control, increase your intake of fruits, vegetables, whole grains, and lean proteins. Incorporate regular physical activity into your routine to support weight loss.</string>
    <string name="obese_class_I">Diet Recommendation: Adopt a balanced diet consisting of whole foods, including plenty of vegetables, fruits, lean proteins, whole grains, and healthy fats. Limit intake of processed foods, sugary beverages, and high-calorie snacks.</string>
    <string name="obese_class_ii">Diet Recommendation: Consult with a healthcare professional or registered dietitian to create a personalized diet plan tailored to your health needs. Focus on gradual weight loss through portion control, regular exercise, and a balanced diet.</string>
</resources>